I'm super happy to tell you about a German brand today
NAKT from Berlin
They make rave outfits, clubbing wear and yes this is going to be one of the outfits today
Despite I'm not into rave music I do think that they're really cool and they would also look great on fetish parties
So let's check them out
This is going to be fun to get into
If you're wondering what kind of outfit this is, it's a bodysuit I'm going to pair it with a harness and pants.
And let me change and then you'll see it.
This is the bodysuit. It took a while to adjust everything that it fits.
But everything is adjustable. That's really cool.
And I'm going to put a pants on top of it so it's not too naked.
And now I need some boots.
and then also a harness but let's start with the boots I think they match really well together
and I'm glad that I'm wearing pants on top of the body suit
but I also got a harness and a choker so let's completely look
again it took a while to adjust everything but it is unisex everything from nact is unisex so
it's great that everything's so adjustable and all the belt bands so some are belt bands
and some are elastics in between so it's really mix and match and mix and match I'm going to add
choker as well. Okay wait a sec. Now there we go. That's cute. I think it's really cute and I think
the whole look is so cool. I feel so badass. With this outfit I can totally go to a goth party or
goth festival but of course it's also clubbing in Ibiza. It's also Burning Man festival. I mean I
I could go to a fetish party as well because it is just such a unique and strappy outfit
and yeah of course you can go to Rafe in Berlin obviously and you can also visit Nakt in Berlin
Broken wings teach me to fly again
I stand alone
I'm not entirely sure if the harness is too much on this outfit. I know I did. I will wear it on
the catsuit as well. So let's try this one without the harness. I just have to see how I get out of
it. I like that. Okay. And this is the look without the harness. I think it's cool as well. It's not
as brutal as with the harness and all the metal parts. A bit more playful, a bit more girly-ish.
so to say. Also nice.
Next outfit is going to be this catsuit and yes I will add the harness again but I also have a belt.
The belt comes with the catsuit so it's a two-piece set and now stupid me
already put on the shoes but I have to get into the harness again.
Okay, so this chain here is attached to the catsuit as a kind of necklace accessory.
And I think the harness looks better here in this outfit although it was also good with
the other one.
Again, mix and match, everything looks good together from NAKT.
And the kit itself is really plain but also really comfy.
It's like a really stretchy and tight t-shirt fabric and the harness is a really nice add-on.
They also have different harnesses so if you don't like this particular one, they have others as well.
again I have to stress this point everything is unisex so if you want to see how this one
looks on a guy go check out the nakt web page and the store because they have pictures thanks so
much to nakt for this cooperation oh by the way nakt is german and means naked just a little fun
fact um yeah what did i want to say oh yeah i do have a discount code check it out in the
description text of course i'll link everything down below give the video a thumbs up tell me
if you like this style because I really do and it is something new on my channel
but I hope you like it too and see you in the next video bye